apexsystems.com 2019-05-15

# Apex | Privacy Policy

YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US

At Apex Systems (“Apex”), we understand how much you value the privacy of your information and will treat any information you share with us accordingly. This Privacy Policy details the ways in which Apex collects and uses personally identifiable information you share with us.

**Collection of Personal Information**

Apex may collect a variety of information from you including information provided on resumes, name, contact information (telephone number(s), email address(es), and physical address(es), etc.), and employment information (previous employment, desired types of future employment, geographical location interests, etc.). Apex may collect this information directly from you through our website or a variety of other sources (email, telephone, etc.), or any other source Apex uses to collect user information. 

**Storage and Use of Personal Information**

Any information Apex collects from or about you may be stored by Apex in one or more database systems maintained by Apex (either directly or indirectly). Apex may process and use this information in order to perform our services. We may additionally use this information to contact you concerning a variety of matters, including, but not limited to, employment opportunities and satisfaction surveys. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

Apex will generally only share your information with third parties in the context of providing its staffing services, and only after an initial screening interview with a recruiter. The only other situations which may lead to Apex disclosing your information include: 

  1. Disclosure to companies and individuals we employ to perform business functions and services on our behalf, and only to the extent necessary for such functions to be performed. Such functions may include, for example, analyzing data, providing legal, accounting and marketing services; and  

  2. Disclosure to the extent necessary or appropriate to government agencies and other third parties in order to comply with applicable laws, the service of legal process, or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law requiring such disclosure; (b) protect Apex’s rights or property; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of the users or the public.

**Cookies**

If your browser is set up to accept cookies, Apex will place cookies on your computer for the purpose of providing you a custom website experience. Apex will also use cookies to collect information on how Apex’s website is used, but will only collect such information in the aggregate and will not associate such information with any of your personally identifiable information. Acceptance of cookies is not necessary to use Apex’s website, and if you wish for Apex’s website not to place cookies on your computer you may alter your browser’s privacy settings accordingly. 

**Security of Information**

While Apex values the security of your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure. Accordingly, Apex cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, either through our website or through any other method, and you make such transmissions at your own risk. Certain portions of our website are protected by 128-bit SSL encryption. These areas can be identified by noting an “https” at the beginning of the web address in the address bar. 

**Privacy Policy Revisions**

Apex reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. When Apex chooses to revise this policy, it will post the updated policy on this website. 

**Privacy Inquiries**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about the information Apex has of you, feel free to contact us by using the contact form on this website or by emailing us at [executivefeedback@apexsystemsinc.com](mailto:executivefeedback@apexsystemsinc.com).
